Finding Aid for Jesse Siddall Reeves pamphlets and reprints
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Jesse Siddall Reeves pamphlets and reprints 1905-1941
Reeves, Jesse Siddall,1872-
1 box
DA 2; R332; P186
Collection of pamphlets and reprints of University of Michhigan political science professor Jesse Siddall Reeves.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Unknown
Periodic additions to the records are not expected.
The collection is open to research.
Professor of Political Science at the University of Michigan
This is a collection of reprints and pamphlets written by Jesse Siddall Reeves and accumulated from different sources. The collection is arranged alphabetically by title name.
Subjects:
International law.
- Pamphlets and reprints
  - Coke of Norfolk and Lafayette, 1938 (Box 1)
  - Coke of Norfolk and Lafayette--II, 1939 (Box 1)
  - La communaute internationale, 1925 (Box 1)
  - An empire builder, 1940 (Box 1)
  - First National Bank of Richmond, Indiana, Appellant, vs. John W. Turner, Treasurer of Wayne County, Appellee, [1901 ?] (Box 1)
  - Fundamental concepts in international law in relation to political theory and legal philosophy, undated (Box 1)
  - Grotius, De jure belli ac pacis; a bibliographical account, [1925] (Box 1)
  - International law in a troubled world, 1940 (Box 1)
  - International society and international law, 1921 (Box 1)
  - The interrelation of the domestic and foreign policies of the nation, 1941 (Box 1)
  - Jeremy Bentham and American jurisprudence, 1906 (Box 1)
  - The justiciability of international disputes, 1916 (Box 1)
  - The league of nations. 1919 (Box 1)
  - Letters of Gideon J. Pillow to James K. Polk, 1844,1906. (Reeves, editor) (Box 1)
  - Prussian-American treaties, [1917] (Box 1)
  - Report of committee to investigate conditions and prospects of the municipal light plant of Richmond, Indiana, 1906 (Box 1)
  - Scholarship, an accomplishment and a profession, 1937 (Box 1)
  - Space and time, 1937 (Box 1)
  - The treaty of Guadalupe-Hidalgo, 1905 (Box 1)
  - Two conceptions of the freedom of the seas, 1917 (Box 1)